{
    "id": "1acbdbde9c21457f898b1f6748b98fdd",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You should do things ……………………. carefully.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was the ……………………… sensible thing to do.",
            "description": "The superlative adjective is usually used with the.",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the …………………………. boy in the class?",
            "description": "The superlative adjective is usually used with the.",
            "answers": [
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was not at all …………………………",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison we use the positive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "amused",
                "more amused",
                "most amused"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The bride smiled ……………………….. at the guests.",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison we use the positive adjective or adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "warmly",
                "more warmly",
                "most warmly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "When I met her yesterday she looked ………………………….. than before.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "healthy",
                "healthier",
                "healthiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Write ………………………… legibly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That was the …………………………… day of my life.",
            "description": "Superlatives are used with the.",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happier",
                "happiest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I earned much …………………….. today than yesterday.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………………… respect for dishonest people.",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison use the positive adjective. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She works ………………………… than anybody I know.",
            "description": "Use the comparative form before than.",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "hardest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am the ……………………….. singer in my family.",
            "description": "Use the superlative form after the.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worser",
                "worst"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}